♪From primal chaos to the starry sky♪
♪In the whole world,
we shall hold the balance♪
♪The cauldron tempers divine blades♪
♪The furnace refines the empty void♪
♪The Way is in mystic fate♪
♪Be brave enough to split
the primal chaos wide open♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel
by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
[Episode 26]
Even if only you and I remain,
I would gladly accept it.
Li Changshou,
I have a question for you.
Answer me truthfully.
Now,
I've ended all your troubles.
From this day on,
none will covet the Pregenesis Sword;
none can threaten us again.
If I were to say now
that I want to spend my life
with you,
♪Someone has unsettled your heart♪
will you accept me?
I...
♪Making me lean down and confirm slowly♪
♪Not knowing what love truly is♪
♪Just as it was at first♪
Bow to each other as a married couple.
♪At storm's end, stars gleam,
and clouds drift♪
♪Together we smile,
watching moonrise and sunset♪
East Sea Dragon Clan, blood for blood!
Little Uncle.
Little Prince.
Senior
Hanzhi...
Little Prince.
Little Prince!
[A few days ago]
[Tranquil and Void]
Rock, paper, scissors!
You lost!
Here, stick this on.
Mentor.
Come on, let's go again.
Little Uncle.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Cansheng.
I'm all alone again.
Who's there?
Who is it?
Who dares trespass on my Turtle Island?
Cansheng?
Is it really you, Cansheng?
Where have you been?
I was worried sick about you.
I thought you were all dead,
leaving me all alone again.
Senior.
You can speak now?
I met someone.
He said
he can help us get revenge.
Revenge?
Avenge ourselves
on the Dragon Clan.
I'll boost your magical power
and make arrangements for you.
Thank you.
Rise.
But first,
you must lure someone for me.
Why isn't Senior back yet?
Senior?
Senior, I'm here!
What are you doing?
Careful!
An assassin!
Pearl Elites,
seize the assassin with me.
Jin Chan.
You...
Do not draw attention.
Wait for the right moment.
Yi!
Guards, seize her!
Little Uncle! Little Uncle!
Dragon King, is this your scheme too?
This is not the Dragon King's doing.
He seeks balance.
He would not harm the Little Prince.
Who is this person?
Why strike at my son?
She knew the Little Prince
as his senior in the Human Clan.
You brought her into the Dragon Palace?
We had no idea she was here.
The Dragon Palace has one gate.
For the past half month,
the Water Dragon Spout
only brought you in.
Perhaps
she had already hidden here
half a month ago
like Bian Zhuang.
Impossible.
If she had hidden for half a month,
she could not escape my eyes.
If it was before that,
Bian Zhuang would have seen her.
Yet he never mentioned her.
Then when did she get in?
Wait.
Before we entered the Dragon Palace,
you opened the Water Dragon Spout once.
When was that?
When the dragon guards
reported Ao Yi's return.
She must have posed as a dragon guard.
[Token]
The Little Prince is coming back.
I'll go inform His Majesty at once.
You've worked hard. Go rest early.
Yes.
Follow me.
Her magical power is weak.
She wouldn't come alone.
Someone inside must be aiding her.
Within the Dragon Palace,
who wants her to murder His Highness?
Jin Chan.
You've indeed
betrayed the Two Saints.
How can this be?
To the great Way of the world,
emptiness is fullness.
No virtue is virtue; no Way is Way.
No face or form
is
thousand faces and forms.
I saved him from the python's jaws.
His soul and spirit are broken.
He is but a walking husk.
I remade him myself.
The man he is now
knows no pain or fear.
He cannot die.
Nor can he truly live.
He became the finest corpse vessel.
Only one thing remains in him:
hatred.
As for you,
killing you
costs much spiritual power.
I cannot spare it now.
But if what happened here
reaches the Two Saints,
what fate would await
your kin in the Blood Sea?
Congratulations.
Westdawn Sect's great cause nears.
Time to choose
your side.
Didn't you say you killed Jin Chan?
Are you sure?
Little rascal's plan
is sure to be foolproof.
I am asking him.
My mole by Jin Chan's side
still hasn't answered.
I don't know.
You don't know?
My original plan
was to take out all Jin Chan's pawns,
leaving him no way out.
But if he's a hidden trump I don't know,
then...
Even if it truly is Jin Chan's doing,
why would he have her
try to kill Ao Yi now?
Is he still wooing
the East Sea Dragon Clan?
This is bad.
We were lured away.
Where are you going?
Jin Chan was never after Ao Yi.
He only wanted to draw us away
to seize the Sword fragment
in the chaos.
Then what are you going to do?
Jin Chan is a man of schemes.
If he sways Ao Guang with words,
we'll be in grave danger.
But
with your strength,
if you go alone,
can you stand against the Dragon King?
Within the East Sea,
only I can restrain the Dragon King.
You cannot go.
You carry a Sword fragment.
So, this time,
you must stay behind.
Do not think
only you can bear it all.
When I first bore my fate,
you were not even reborn yet.
Yunxiao.
Watch out.
Do not worry.
I'm Seizing Sect's war goddess.
Trust me.
Hold them all down.
This woman is deeply guilty.
She's beyond forgiveness.
Do not let her run. Hold her.
Your clan harmed so many
and ruined so much land.
Who is truly beyond forgiveness?
You are framing me.
Bah.
Young lady, mind your manners.
Besides,
what does that have to do with me?
I'm a turtle.
Your clan destroyed my people
and killed my Little Uncle.
Insolence!
This girl...
Princess Jiang Si'er?
No. What is happening?
Get up. Get up!
My legs!
Ao Yi.
Si'er.
Jia.
I won.
Now,
I cast you off.
By His Majesty's decree, Jiang Si'er
will marry Second Prince Ao Yi
of East Sea.
How did it come to this?
It never used to be like this.
Jiang Si'er.
We were so close.
Have you forgotten?
Who?
Si'er.
Ao Jia.
How shameless!
You used low tricks to stop my wedding!
Why are you here?
You know perfectly well.
Explain yourself clearly.
I must have been blind.
I once thought you were a hero.
Now, you're just a scoundrel.
I...
What are you talking about?
Seize her!
Stop!
Si'er.
Your Highness.
Step back.
It's dangerous!
Your Highness.
Step back!
Why
did you insult me?
She insulted the First Prince.
That's unforgivable!
Gag her!
Did I ask you?
Why
are you here?
Why did you attack me?
Why call me a shameless scoundrel?
Explain them
one by one.
You really don't know?
No more questions. Tell me.
You plotted with Westdawn Sect secretly.
You betrayed the Dragon Palace
of the East Sea
and abducted me here.
What are you plotting?
Can anyone explain this to me?
Still making excuses?
You still won't admit it?
I abducted you?
I betrayed the Dragon Palace?
When did I ever...
Seize her.
Ao Jia.
Your Highness.
Do not be deceived.
She is not Princess Jiang Si'er.
So, it was you.
Princess, you honor me too much.
It is not just me.
It's everyone here.
Your Highness.
Do not listen to him.
Who am I?
- Your Highness.
- Who am I?
Your Highness.
At the Crystal Palace,
Princess Jiang Si'er
turned her back on you.
Yes.
Ao Jia.
They all turned on me.
- Don't listen to him.
- You all turned on me.
Remember who you are.
Do not become someone's puppet.
Puppet?
- What is a puppet?
- The Little Prince is ungrateful.
He is marrying Princess Jiang Si'er now.
Ao Jia.
- Marrying?
- Don't listen to him.
- She is marrying him?
- You are the First Prince.
Pull yourself together.
What are you talking about?
This person is wanted in East Sea.
She's good at enchanting men.
Your Highness, be careful!
Your Highness.
I'm Jiang Si'er.
I'm Jiang Si'er, Your Highness.
Please remember me.
Your Highness.
- Remember me!
- Shut up!
You lied to me.
That's not true.
- Yes, she lied to you.
- Remember me!
- You lied to me.
- That's not true.
Your Highness.
Kill her.
Yes.
Strike!
Your Highness.
Strike! Strike!
Strike!
So, with these demonic arts,
you controlled me for ten years
and made me crave blood
and hunger for slaughter.
Is that it?
Did you think a true East Sea dragon
would not see through your tricks?
Before you die, hear this:
Never look down on the Dragon Clan.
So, these past ten years,
you've been under their control.
I truly wasn't myself.
It's okay.
From this day on,
you are yourself again.
Si'er,
I'm truly sorry.
I made too many mistakes.
We'll break out together
and save the East Sea.
The enemy is upon us.
Why are you staring at me?
I just think
this feels so familiar.
It reminds me of the cultivation art
we practiced here.
Do you remember it all?
It's been ten years.
How could I ever forget?
Master Jin Chan.
It was you after all.
Your Majesty.
Long time no see.
As I recall, in our last meeting,
our places
seemed quite reversed.
You lured me to catch Lan Ling'e
and set me against Ascendance Sect.
When two sides clash,
the watcher takes the prize.
You deceived us with a false death.
Yet you plotted in the shadows.
Without a false death,
how could I fool
two top masterminds behind the scenes?
Do you not fear that I
will make that death real today?
Do you truly think
you can do that?
The Sword fragment is there.
You may take it yourself.
Is it an ambush or a decoy?
What?
You don't want it?
Then I shall take it away.
If you came for the Sword fragment,
you could leave once you took it.
Why stay here?
So, you must be scheming.
You're truly brilliant.
I cannot help but admire you.
So, I feel compelled
to offer you advice.
You have two paths now:
Take
one step forward
and kill me,
so you can remove the threat forever.
Or
run for your life
while there is still time.
You...
Will you truly open the Eye of the Sea?
You know better than anyone
how dreadful what follows will be.
I still have one magic treasure.
Even an Empyreal Aureate Immortal
may fall.
What magic treasure is he hiding?
Fairy Yunxiao.
It seems you
have a third path now.
Why not step back for now
and let Yunxiao test me?
Then, you'll see
whether I'm truly prepared
or merely putting on a show.
Since you are here,
why not show yourself?
Is it your sect's skill
to skulk in the shadows?
That is why I
dare not show myself.
I know your voice.
Back then,
you lured me to seize
the Sea-Calming Pillar.
Yunxiao, you still remember
that we once joined hands.
I was deeply honored.
Joined hands?
You are just a conceited madman
who used me as a pawn.
You wanted a magic treasure.
I needed support.
We could've each gotten what we wanted.
We should have worked as one.
Unfortunately, you chose the wrong foe.
At Ascendance Sect,
you killed many of my Seizing kin.
Their deaths
were worth it.
Nonsense.
They died
for more people's lives.
They died for the whole Seizing Sect.
What did you say?
Had they not died,
when the Great Tribulation came,
the whole Seizing Sect
would perish.
Come out. Explain yourself.
Why are you so obsessed
with gathering innate magic treasures?
And why did your nature change?
Why have you become more violent?
Who did you meet?
What are you truly afraid of?
Silence.
Silence!
Let me tell you, Yunxiao,
what
your deepest fear is.
A mere formation?
This stone wall...
This formation is
the Nine-Turn Formation.
You have sharp eyes.
It is Trifairy Isle's secret formation.
Only we four siblings can set it.
Where did you steal it from?
When did I ever say
I set this formation?
This is the Trifairy Isle
one year later.
Nonsense.
Bixiao and Qiongxiao wield great power.
Zhao Gongming tops
Seizing Sect's outer sect.
With those three guarding it,
who could breach Trifairy Isle?
Senior!
Run!
Zhao Gongming was trapped
by vile sorcery.
His soul and spirit scattered.
He coughed blood and died.
Nothing could save him.
Senior, how did this happen?
Who did this to you?
Tell me who harmed you.
Go, now.
Your junior, Qiongxiao,
tried to save Zhao Gongming.
She went to seize the Book of Curses,
but a magic treasure struck her.
Her soul was destroyed.
Qiongxiao...
Your young junior, Bixiao,
was overcome with terror.
She begged bitterly for mercy,
yet she was drawn in
by the enemy's treasure.
She melted into a pool of blood
and perished.
It's my fault.
We should've listened to you
and run when we knew we couldn't win.
We really couldn't win.
We really couldn't.
Senior.
It is nothing.
It's fine.
Yunxiao, it's nothing.
I'm fine.
It's just a scratch.
Senior!
The Great Calamity has begun.
No one can stop it.
All in Seizing Sect will fall.
None shall survive.
This
is the Fated Mandate.
With me here,
who'd dare do this?
If demons seek my end,
I'll purge demons.
If deities seek my end,
I'll slay the deities.
If heaven wants me dead,
I'll shatter heaven.
My fate isn't up to you.
It's up to me.
Yunxiao.
Little rascal.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have let you go alone.
Don't worry.
I've overcome all inner demons.
Really?
You're not...
Oh, your weakness
is this man.
You...
That's not Lotus Hall!
That's...
That's the Rank-XII Golden Lotus!
Si'er.
Mermaid Princess Jiang Si'er,
please accept my bow.
Your Highness.
Let me finish.
If not for you today,
I don't know how much longer
I would've been under their control.
You've done me a great service.
But
I don't know how much
you've suffered for my sake
all these years.
But rest assured.
I'll repay you
a hundredfold, a thousandfold.
Your Highness.
The man I see before me today
is the First Prince
of the East Sea I once loved.
Let's break out of here together
and save the East Sea.
Sure.
Let's go find Father
and report everything.
Your Highness.
Where might you be going?
He was the one who took me.
The one behind it all.
Where is Jinli?
You mean your planted turncoat?
His cover was blown.
I dealt with him on the spot.
Such a pity.
Our grand plan was nearly done.
Yet he fell at the last moment.
Still,
it changes little.
The Eye of the Sea will open.
All of you
are doomed.
Do you know
what opening the Eye of the Sea means?
All living beings will perish.
Heaven and earth will shatter.
Knowing this,
why do you still insist on that?
Because
this is heaven's will.
Your Highness, waste no words.
I'll hold him here.
Go to the Crystal Palace
and save the Little Prince.
Ao Yi?
Too late.
Ao Yi
is already gone.
Ao Yi.
Can you truly save him?
I've used my exclusive Heartward Spell
to protect his heart.
He's safe for now.
Then why isn't he waking up?
The blade was cursed.
Being struck by it causes a coma.
If the curse isn't broken
within two hours,
his life will be in danger.
Senior, don't be so calm.
Hurry and break the curse!
It's hard to break from outside.
It requires
the Little Prince's own will.
Only then is there a slim chance.
His own will?
He must have
the will to survive.
Someone, please save me.
Someone, save me.
Father.
Jia.
Senior.
Can anyone save me?
No one
can save you.
Master Jin Chan.
Jin Chan.
Master Jin Chan, save me.
Your Highness,
you've fallen into Avici Hell.
No one can save you.
Impossible.
My father is
an Empyreal Aureate Immortal.
He can surely save me.
Yi.
You still haven't grown up.
You've greatly disappointed me.
Father.
I... I...
I've always wanted to revive
the Dragon Palace, Father!
You bear the Dragon's Prophecy.
I once had hope for you.
But you...
You've greatly disappointed me.
Father.
You want to revive the Dragon Clan?
Jia.
I'm not your brother.
You conspired with outsiders
to harm me,
with no regard for our brotherly bond.
I've wasted years caring for you
and protecting you.
That's not true.
I was a fool to trust you.
Jia, just let me explain.
You lied to me.
Senior.
Don't call me Senior.
You vile dragon!
Your clan wiped out my whole clan.
And now, you dare pose
as my Little Uncle?
Senior.
I've been looking for you, Senior.
Looking for me?
You were marrying Si'er
in the Dragon Palace.
Where would you've found me?
You didn't come to me.
So, I came to you.
Alright?
Why?
You've greatly disappointed me.
You're so ungrateful.
You liar!
Senior.
You've greatly disappointed me.
Father.
Ungrateful!
Jia.
You are a liar.
You've greatly disappointed me.
Ungrateful!
That's not true.
You liar! Liar!
You've greatly disappointed me.
You liar!
Ungrateful!
You've greatly disappointed me.
Liar!
Senior.
No!
Have you considered
who brought all of this
upon you?
Trust yourself. You can do it.
Who lured you
away from East Sea
and drew you back again?
Who made you brothers turn
on each other?
Did I hurt Jia?
You two
will have time to make amends.
Right now,
we must make use of this victory.
Who stopped you
from seeking your senior?
When you become King of East Sea,
with Celestial Court behind you,
finding one person will be easy.
And who stripped
your spiritual power
and made you suffer so much?
Why is this spot so hard to wash?
It's fine.
I have deep-clean mode.
Here it comes.
How can this be?
How
could it be him?
♪See mortal joys and sorrows♪
♪Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds♪
♪Alas, love has many twists and turns♪
♪Memories filled with sorrow♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪
♪Down a few more cups of wine♪
♪Through land and sea,
I ask you to come♪
♪For honor's sake, upright and grand♪
♪Alas, our story is short♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tears fall, this fate's not done♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪